<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp-Oradea</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="OradeaFortress_title">Oradea Fortress</string>
    <string name="fortress_description">The Oradea Fortress is the most famous building of Oradea, with an almost millenary history,
        the first signs dating its setup are during the Hungarian King Ladislaus I (1077-1095).
        The fortress is the city\’s emblematic symbol and an historical masterpiece.
 \n\n The Oradea Fortress is unique in Eastern Europe through its complex architectural old
        Italian and military-style fortified bastions kept relatively good condition.</string>
    <string name="oradea_bazar_tilte"> Oradea Bazar</string>
    <string name="oradea_bazar_description">Here was the first cinema, the Edison Theater,
        which had arranged the chairs in the amphitheater, and an English buffet.
        \n\n Now, after more than 100 years, the situation seems little changed.
        This building houses shops, the Irish Pub Restaurant, and in the passage between the
        Republic Square Theater Square, there are book sellers.
\n\n In the center, the pedestrian passage is dominated by a very decorated tympanum in its upper part,
        still preserving the city\'s emblem.</string>
    <string name="house_adorjan1_title"> Adorjan House I</string>
    <string name="house_adorjan1_description">located in the extension of the Theater Depot,
        on its left side, on Str. Patriots corner with Str. Moscow, was built in 1903 by Sztarill Ferencz
        according to the plans of architects Komor Marcell and Jakab Dezső. The secession style,
        loaded and heavy, with great importance for the loading of details, is "complete" by appealing to folkloric
        ornamental solutions.</string>
    <string name="adorjan_house2_title">Adorjan House II</string>
    <string name="adorjan_house2_description">The facade of the building is richly ornamented,
        the frontispiece and around the windows are floral motifs.
        \n\nBetween the windows of the first floor I see the hearts above which are seen flower pots and flower bouquets.
        The heart-shaped window in the upper register is surrounded by bouquets of flowers</string>
    <string name="deutsch_house_title">Deutsch House</string>
    <string name="deutsch_house_description"> Deutsch House is a historic monument building in Oradea.
        \n\nIt was built between 1906 and 1910, after Sztarill Ferenc\'s project.
        The entire facade of the two-story building is decorated with popular, floral motifs.
        The upper part of the floor ends in semicircles, and in the middle there is a trilobal tympanum
        with a window in the middle, in the shape of a rounded heart.</string>
    <string name="fuchsl_house_title">Fuchsl Palace</string>
    <string name="fuchsl_house_description">The historic monument building, located on Independentei 11-13,
        known as the Fuchsl House, was built between 1902-1903.
        The feature of this high-floor, two-storey building is the "mismatch" between its rectangular structure and the
        curvilinear expression of the facades.
        The rectangular structure is transvested in a curvilinear way through the sinusoidal cornice of the sheet and the
        valved profile of the profile under the cornice. The facade is flat (only the corner is rounded and ends with a tower)
        with rectangular windows, trapezoidal panels with reliefs. The windows of the attic have kidney-shaped windows.
        The balcony of the balconies and the access portal are decorated with vegetal elements.</string>
    <string name="ursuline_complex_title">Ursuline Complex</string>
    <string name="ursuline_complex_description">The complex of the church and monastery features architectural elements both baroque
        and romantic with Neo-Gothic influences. The construction seems to have been completed in 1877,
        when the wings on the Calea Republicii are added to the current street of Moscow, no. 1-3, where the
        "Ady Endre" High School currently operates.</string>
    <string name="ortpalace_title">The diocese of Oradea</string>
    <string name="ortpalace_description">This building was the palace of the famous architect, Rimanóczy Kálmán junior.
        The edifice built in 1905 is part of the new wave of buildings built in the early twentieth century.
        In 1921 the building was bought by the Orthodox Church. On the first floor there was a chapel.
        In 1971 the building was renovated, the chandelier windows were changed with stained glass, the paintings were
        restored, and what remained of the old palace - stoves and mural ornaments - were restored by specialists.
        Next to the chapel is a museum, where objects of worship, old books, manuscripts, silverware, golden silverware,
        icons on glass, paintings, etc. are displayed.</string>
    <string name="med_faculty_title">The faculty of Medicine</string>
    <string name="med_faculty_description">The building where the Faculty of Medicine Oradea currently operates,
        Was built in eclectic style in 1894 by Rimanoczy Kalman Junior.
        Here too, in the Cris area, they have editorial offices and cultural societies.</string>
    <string name="astoria_hotel_title">Astoria Hotel</string>
    <string name="astoria_hotel_description">It is an edifice that has not changed its destination over time.
        The EMKE Hotel, since then, was designed by Sztarill Ferenc in 1902 in secession style with Gothic prints.
        The building has a high ground floor where a café was set up, the favorite meeting place for writers, poets and journalists.
        On the wall of the literary café a commemorative plaque informs us that it was the favorite place of the great Hungarian poet
        Ady Endre, a prominent personality of the literary group who managed to print in 1908 the "A holnap" anthology.</string>
    <string name="apollo_palace_title">Apollo Palace</string>
    <string name="apollo_palace_description">The Apollo Palace was built between 1912-1914. In his style, the Berlin secession, has some
        decorations that remind of the Empire style. This building is the last work of the renowned builder Rimanóczy Kálmán junior, who
        died prematurely. At present, the ground floor of the building houses the Unique Store</string>
    <string name="Rivo_resturant_title">Rivo Restaurant &amp; Lounge</string>
    <string name="Rivo_restaurant_description">\"The place is amazing, a big terrace on the river, and in winter the full window wall give a comfortable harmful sensation even the restaurant look is of modern design.
The hamburger with ceddar cheese, bacon and onions is very, very good.
People are gentle and professional but when is full you should be patient. The reward will surely be the food.
Nice place to return.\"</string>
    <string name="spoon_restaurant_title">Spoon Restaurant</string>
    <string name="spoon_restaurant_description">\"The first impression attracts people to come and have a sit.
Chairs and sofas are tremendously comfortable, music is nice and not too heavy, and most of all the interior
        decoration is outstanding!
The menu is classic, with a lot of choice however.\"</string>
    <string name="ristretto_title">Ristretto</string>
    <string name="ristretto_description">Those guys and girls really take care of what they do.
The coffe and cappuccino are equal and better than many you can find in Italy.
The bar tender can explain you the techniques and the passion they put in their coffee products.
Are also good the hot choccolates (but only in winter) and for summer time the cold lemonade with mint.</string>
    <string name="corsarul_title">Corsarul</string>
    <string name="corsarul_description">In Oradea, Corsar is known as one of the traditional restaurants in Oradea. Restaurant Corsar offers you both drinks and menus for the most refined
        tastes, as well as a welcoming and experienced staff for your taste.</string>
    <string name="american_grill_title">American Grill</string>
    <string name="america_grill_description">American Grill is an American-style restaurant that wants to offer an alternative to eating in the city
    (classic restaurants and fast-food restaurants), the fast-casted restaurant.</string>
    <string name="hanul_cu_noroc_title">Hanul cu noroc</string>
    <string name="hanul_cu_noroc_description">\"This is one of the best price/quality restaurants in town, a great variety of foods, serving is
        not always perfect but overall its ok\"</string>
    <string name="lactobar_title">Lactobar RetroBistro</string>
    <string name="lactobar_description">Situated on the pedestrian street right in the heart of the city, Lactobar
        Retro Bistro is a new concept for the Oradea market.
        With a special design meant to remind us of the past and with a menu to suit, the locality attracts
        a varied clientele.
The locality seems to have an easy American, but we can find Romanian
        specialties such as lard or eggplant.</string>
    <string name="lords_title">Lord\'s Pub</string>
    <string name="lords_description">\" The best place to spend your evenings. Great atmosphere created by the friendly people and the music played in there. From my point of view, i can say that this is the best pub in town.
        I highly recommend at least a pint of Guinnes for a good beginning of your night.\"</string>
    <string name="moscka_title">Moszkva Caffe</string>
    <string name="mosca_description">\"It is a multicultural center, located in a beautiful but rundown Art Nouveau building in the city center a few meters from the theater. With is mismatched furniture and graffitis,it is very
        popular among the younger generation. Excellent and affordable coctails.\"</string>
    <string name="excess_title">Excess Whisky &amp; Bitter Bar</string>
    <string name="excess_description">\"Amazing cocktails and drinks. Quality service. Skillful bartenders. A simple yet classy location. Great for a quick coffee, business meeting or a night out.\"</string>
    <string name="life_title">Life Club</string>
    <string name="life_description">The Life Club, set up in a building on Alexandru Vlahuţă Street, in the area where the former Traffic Club functioned until last year, is tailored to everyone\'s taste.
Fridays are reserved for manele lovers, and Saturday evenings are dedicated to dancing, with dance evenings organized here. With a very special and elegant look, Club Life offers everything for everyone:
        from manele and live music to clubbing music.</string>
    <string name="select_poker_title">Select Poker Club</string>
    <string name="select_poker_description">Select Poker Club Oradea is the ideal place where you can play 100% live poker with logistics and professional staff.
Select Poker Club offers 9 permanent poker tables, of which 3 are cash and 6 tournaments. From Monday to Friday and Sunday are tournaments, including satellites
        in PokerFest events, with which our club is an official partner, events in special or traditional formats such as Freezeout, Knockout, Deepstack Turbo, Win The Button, Omaha and so on.
The club addresses both experienced players, those who are keen on big stakes, and beginners or small-scale recreational
        players who just want to have fun at a table once in a while.</string>
    <string name="green_title">Green Pub</string>
    <string name="green_description">\"We met some friends for drinks here,being in Oradea overnight.
The place is clean and the staff was kind.
The beer cold..what else is there:-)\"</string>
    <string name="black_title">Black Eagle Pub</string>
    <string name="black_description">If you stay in the center of Oradea, you will discover the wonders of an authentic Irish pub. You will be glad and entertained with the best friends of relaxation:
        Guinness beer, good music and incendiary atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="double_hotel_title">DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel </string>
    <string name="double_hotel_description">DoubleTree by Hilton Oradea is located in the green area of ​​one of the most beautiful cities in Romania, Oradea. Enjoy a delicious DoubleTree cookery at
        the time of arrival and let our friendly staff drive you to your room or apartment. All the rooms in our hotel are modernly decorated with top-quality finishes, home-like internet access,
        large TVs and spacious desks to provide you with a comfortable and relaxing stay. Swim in the hotel\'s indoor pool or relax in the hot tub.</string>
    <string name="ramada_hotel_title">Ramada Hotel</string>
    <string name="ramada_hotel_description">Hotel Ramada Oradea enjoys a convenient location in Oradea, less than a 2-minute drive from the historic city center, and offers free access to the Riserva Wine Spa,
        which includes a fitness center, 2 saunas, a salt cave, A seating room and a terrace with 2 jacuzzis and panoramic views of the old town. Free WiFi is available in all areas.</string>
    <string name="continental_forum_title">Continental Forum Hotel</string>
    <string name="continental_forum_description">Continental Forum Oradea is a 4-star hotel in Oradea, located right in the city center and also the largest hotel in Oradea. The hotel offers high quality accommodation in Oradea,
        being one of the most famous hotels in Oradea. Once you have crossed the threshold, you will be convinced of the quality of its services.</string>
    <string name="astoria_hotel_hotel_description">Hotel Astoria Oradea, a superb 4 star hotel, built in a perfect place: in the city center. You can enjoy a breathtaking panorama of historic buildings such as the Regina Maria Theater,
    Poynar House and Hotel Transilvania.</string>
    <string name="elite_hotel_title"> Elite Hotel</string>
    <string name="elite_hotel_description">Quietly located in Oradea\'s I.C.Brătianu Park, Elite Hotel has a thermal pool and free Wi-Fi.
        The rooms are stylish and air-conditioned.
Rich breakfast buffets are served in the breakfast room. Breakfast can also be brought to your room.
The Elite Hotel\'s pool has free access. The hot tub offers free access from 18:00 to 20:00. It is located inside.</string>
    <string name="class_hotel_title">Class Hotel</string>
    <string name="class_hotel_description">Class Hotel enjoys a quiet location, 1.5 km from the center of Oradea. It features a sauna and an outdoor pool.
        It offers free Wi-Fi and free on-site parking.
All rooms have air conditioning, private bathroom, cable TV and a balcony.</string>
    <string name="robinson_title">Robinson Country</string>
    <string name="robinson_description">At the entrance under the wooden pod is a small lake, populated with exotic fish andwater lilies.
        Camping Robinson Country, Oradea,
The pool is surrounded by five cottages.
The swimming pool also functions as a swimming pool.
        The entrance ticket is 30 lei, the whole amount is consumable in the bar or in the camping restaurant.</string>
    <string name="nymphaea_title">Nymphaea Aquapark</string>
    <string name="nymphaea_description">Discover the largest Aquapark in this region of Europe, the Nymphaea Aquapark. Spread over an area of 7 hectares, it will bring you into the fascinating world of fun and adrenaline.
        A new way to get rid of the alert and stressful pace of the city will conquer you in the first few moments.</string>
    <string name="historic">"Historical\nPlaces</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="night_life">NightLife</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
</resources>
